import 'package:flutter/material.dart';

List<Map> QuestionBank = [
  {
    'id': 1,
    'question': "1.On_______ is Replublic Day of india?",
    'A': '15 August',
    'B': '8 September',
    'C': '14 January',
    'D': '26 January',
    'answer': 'D',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.orange,
  },
  {
    'id': 2,
    'question': "2.How many districts are there in Gujrat?",
    'A': '31',
    'B': '32',
    'C': '33',
    'D': '34',
    'answer': 'C',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.purple,
  },
  {
    'id': 3,
    'question': "3.How many Types Of Gradient?",
    'A': '1',
    'B': '2',
    'C': '3',
    'D': '4',
    'answer': 'C',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.lightGreen,
  },
  {
    'id': 4,
    'question': "4.How many Akshardham in India?",
    'A': '1',
    'B': '2',
    'C': '3',
    'D': '4',
    'answer': 'B',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.blue,
  },
  {
    'id': 5,
    'question': "5.10/2+3-7?",
    'A': '0',
    'B': '1',
    'C': '2',
    'D': '3',
    'answer': 'B',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.redAccent,
  },
  {
    'id': 6,
    'question': "6.Which of the Capital of the Gujrat.",
    'A': 'patan',
    'B': 'div',
    'C': 'Gandhinagar',
    'D': 'None of the above',
    'answer': 'C',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.brown,
  },
  {
    'id': 7,
    'question': "7.Which of the Capital of the india.",
    'A': 'patan',
    'B': 'Delhi',
    'C': 'Gandhinagar',
    'D': 'None of the above',
    'answer': 'B',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.grey,
  },
  {
    'id': 8,
    'question': "8.How many types of Widget.",
    'A': '1',
    'B': '2',
    'C': '3',
    'D': '4',
    'answer': 'B',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.red.shade800,
  },
  {
    'id': 9,
    'question': "9. How many types of Button.",
    'A': '5',
    'B': '6',
    'C': '2',
    'D': 'None of the above',
    'answer': 'A',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.amber,
  },
  {
    'id': 10,
    'question': "10.Who is Current Home Minister of India",
    'A': 'Rahul Gandhi',
    'B': 'Narendra Modi',
    'C': 'Amit Shah',
    'D': 'Bhupendra Patel',
    'answer': 'D',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.indigo,
  },
];
